♪ Baby, tell me if you like it ♪
♪ It's me and you, now ♪
♪ I've been waiting ♪
♪ Think I wanna make
that move, now ♪
♪ Baby, tell me
how you like it ♪
♪♪
♪ Uh ♪
♪ Next selection ♪
♪ Bad boy ♪
♪ You've been waiting so long ♪
♪ I'm here to answer your call ♪
♪ I know that I shouldn't
have had you waiting at all ♪
♪ I've been so busy, but
I've been thinking 'bout ♪
♪ What I wanna do with you ♪
♪ I know them other guys,
they been talking 'bout ♪
♪ The way I do what I do ♪
♪ They heard I was good,
they wanna see if it's true ♪
♪ They know you're the
one I wanna give it to ♪
♪ I can see you want me too ♪
-♪ Now, it's me and you ♪
-♪ It's me and you, now,
I've been waiting ♪
♪ Think I wanna make that move,
now, baby, tell me
if you like it ♪
-♪ Tell me if you like it ♪
-♪ It's me and you, now,
I've been waiting ♪
-♪ Think I wanna make
that move, now ♪
-♪ Gonna make that move now ♪
♪ Baby, tell me
how you like it ♪
♪ I was waiting for you to
tell me you were ready ♪
♪ I know what to do, if
only you would let me ♪
♪ As long as you're cool with
it, I'll treat you right ♪
♪ Here is where you wanna be ♪
♪ I know them other guys,
they been talking 'bout ♪
♪ The way I do what I do ♪
♪ They heard I was good,
they wanna see if it's true ♪
♪ They know you're the
one I wanna give it to ♪
♪ I can see you want me too ♪
-♪ And now, it's me and you ♪
-♪ It's me and you, now ♪
♪ I've been waiting ♪
♪ Think I wanna make
that move ♪
♪ I'm thinking 'bout
making that move ♪
♪ Baby, tell me if you like it ♪
-♪ Tell me if you like it ♪
-♪ It's me and you, now,
I've been waiting ♪
-♪ Think I wanna make
that move, now ♪
-♪ Hey, gonna make a move ♪
♪ Baby, tell me
how you like it, yeah ♪
♪ Baby, I'll love you
all the way down ♪
♪ Get you right
where you like it ♪
♪ I promise you'll
like it, I swear ♪
♪ Just relax and let
me make that move,
it's our secret thang ♪
♪ We'll keep it
between me and you ♪
-♪ It's me and you, now ♪
-♪ I've been waiting ♪
-♪ Think I wanna make
that move, now ♪
-♪ Gonna make that move now ♪
♪ Baby, tell me if you like it ♪
-♪ Tell me if you like it ♪
-♪ It's me and you, now ♪
-♪ Yea, yea ♪
-♪ I've been waiting ♪
-♪ Think I wanna make
that move, now ♪
-♪ Gonna make a move ♪
♪ Baby, tell me
how you like it ♪
-♪ Me and you ♪
-♪ It's me and you, now ♪
-♪ I've been waiting ♪
-♪ It's just me and you ♪
-♪ It's just us two ♪
-♪ Think I wanna make
that move, now ♪
-♪ It's just me and you ♪
-♪ Baby, tell me if you like it♪
-♪ It's me and you, now ♪
-♪ I've been waiting
for your love ♪
-♪ Gonna make a move ♪
-♪ Think I wanna make
that move, now ♪
♪ Baby, tell me
how you like it ♪
♪♪